<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben Basuni</title>
    <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ben Basuni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stampedethegoat.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 - Outside the Window</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/1/window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/1/window/</guid>
      <description>Day 1: Outside the Window What’s the weather outside your window doing right now?
If that’s not inspiring, what’s the weather like somewhere you wish you could be?
The weather outside is currently cloudy. It was raining earlier, but now it’s actually fine. I’m thinking I should learn a new vocabulary word every single day. That way I can improve my writing &amp;amp; insert all sorts of imagination into my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 - Love Poem</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/2/love-poem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/2/love-poem/</guid>
      <description>Day 2: The Unrequited Love Poem How do you feel when you love someone who does not love you back?
I really don’t mind it. Because I love myself, when I know that I deeply love myself, there isn’t anyone in the world that I know that can make me feel bad.
Because I am the universe, I am the ocean. Perhaps not as vast or expansive as the actual thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 - The Vessel</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/3/vessel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/3/vessel/</guid>
      <description>Day 3: The Vessel Write about a ship or other vehicle that can take you somewhere different from where you are right now.
The Tesla Model 3 is one of the sickest cars that I’ve ever been into. With the self drive capability, the simplistic and minimalist style, that’s what I want right there. Midnight black.
As much as I appreciate the car that I have right now, it still gives me a worrisome mindset sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 - Dancing</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/4/dancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/4/dancing/</guid>
      <description>Day 4: Dancing Who’s dancing and why are they tapping those toes?
CJ is dancing because he’s at a competition this weekend. He’s tapping those toes because that’s his hobby, that’s what he enjoys doing. As others enjoy different things, dancers love to dance.
In a sense, are we not all dancing in one form or another. Whether it is dancing in our actions, in a simple dialogue that we have with one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 - Breakfast</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/5/breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/5/breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Day 5: What’s for Breakfast What’s for breakfast? Dinner? Lunch? Or maybe you could write a poem about that time you met a friend in that cafe.
I had an omelet today for breakfast with toast, then I added a banana as the fruit after I was done eating &amp;amp; had me some old brew after I was done.
I was very satisfied with my food. With just a little effort, I had a breakfast like a king!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 - Eye Contact</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/6/eye-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/6/eye-contact/</guid>
      <description>Day 6: Eye Contact Write about 2 people seeing each other for the first time.
Two people staring at each other for the first time. I suppose if both of them had the courage to stare at one another in the eye, there is a level of courage and interest that both feel for the other.
A staring of the eyes is a deep dive into the spirit. A soul is most visible through the eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 - Rocket Ship</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/7/rocket-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/7/rocket-ship/</guid>
      <description>Day 7: The Rocket Ship Write about a Rocket Ship on its way to the moon or a distant galaxy.
A rocket ship on its way to the moon or a distant galaxy. Isn’t that similar to what we are all doing? I feel like I’m currently on a rocket ship going to a distant galaxy as well. It’s like we were born here on Earth but there wasn’t much that we could do to find similarities between what was actually home versus if we were actually going to a distant galaxy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 - Dream Catcher</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/8/dream-catcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/8/dream-catcher/</guid>
      <description>Day 8: Dream Catcher Write something inspired by a recent dream you had.
The dream that I remember is about a mini reunion that my high school friends and I had. We had a good time, but I felt like I was disconnected from them.
It’s like when I found myself. I disconnected from others but when I had found myself, then I try to connect with others. But at the end of it all, it comes down to being comfortable with yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 - Animal</title>
      <link>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/9/animal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stampedethegoat.github.io/writing/9/animal/</guid>
      <description>Day 9: Animal Choose an Animal. Write about it!
I choose a turtle today for my animal to write about. The turtle is a wise figure, a wise animal. I don’t think it’s been considered as a joke or a silly animal ever in the history that I’ve read books and stories. Maybe TNMT is the one that might be different, but even that they’re more like teenage boys that they are turtles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>